A Guide to the Policy Office: General Assembly Legislation of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1990-1993.
Library of Virginia
- General Assembly Legislation, 1990.
  - Senate Bills, 1990.
    - SB 478 (90) Special Advisory Commission on Mandated Health Insurance Benefits, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - SB 479 (90) Accident and sickness insurance, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - SB 480 (90) Accident and sickness insurance, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - SB 481 (90) Virginia Indigent Health Care Trust Fund, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - SB 482 (90) Virginia Indigent Health Care Trust Fund, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - SB 483 (90) Primary Health Care System, Statewide Area Health Education Center Program, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - SB 484 (90) Certificates of public need, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - SB 487 (90) Distribution of drugs to minors, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - SB 488 (90) Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - SB 489 (90) Indebtedness and bond issues - Cities, towns, counties, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - SB 491 (90) Noise ordinances - Sport shooting ranges, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - SB 493 (90) Standards of quality, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - SB 495 (90) Providers of services for Medicaid recipients, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - SB 496 (90) Medicaid New Drug Review Act, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - SB 498 (90) Planning districts and commissions, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - SB 499 (90) Licensed asbestos and RFS contractors, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - SB 500 (90) Virginia Economic Development Revolving Trust, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - SB 501 (90) Appointments by the Governor, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Amended / Reenrolled Legislation, 1990.
    - HB 30 (90) Appropriations Act / Budget Bill, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - HB 32 (90) Capital Projects - Institutions of Higher Learning, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - HB 33 (90) Capital Projects, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - HB 43 (90) Exemption from property tax - Virginia Mountain Housing, Inc., 1990. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - HB 91 (90) Consolidation - Roanoke City / Roanoke County, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - HB 108 (90) Town Charter - Clinchco, Dickenson County, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - HB 129 (90) Local Anti-Drug Trust Fund Authority, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - HB 188 (90) Liability of trust, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - HB 197 (90) Subdivision ordinances, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - HB 208 (90) School crossings, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - HB 222 (90) Chemical tests to determine alcohol/drug content of blood, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - HB 230 (90) Charitable solicitations, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - HB 241 (90) Campaign contributions - Surplus funds, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - HB 250 (90) Alcoholic Beverage Control laws - Public places, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - HB 337 (90) Malicious destruction of property, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - HB 341 (90) Sheriff duties, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - HB 351 (90) Collection agencies - Delinquent taxes, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - HB 387 (90) Body armor - Violent crime, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - HB 397 (90) Virginia Personnel Act - Grievance, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - HB 425 (90) Escehats, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - HB 461 (90) Daycare programs, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - HB 487 (90) Supplemental licenses of motor vehicle dealers, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - HB 505 (90) Pre-payment of loans - Rule of 78 rebate method, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - HB 533 (90) Property exemptions, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - HB 547 (90) District courts - Filing motions for judgments, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - HB 560 (90) Forfeiture of weapons used in the commission of a criminal offense, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - HB 572 (90) Political subdivisions - Declaration of emergency, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - HB 590 (90) Personal watercraft, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - HB 624 (90) Issuance of bonds, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - HB 663 (90) Abatement of nuisances involving drugs, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - HB 678 (90) Forfeiture of license for driving while intoxicated, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - HB 688 (90) Child support enforcement, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - HB 698 (90) Shooting firearms from motor vehicles, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - HB 706 (90) Athlete agencies, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - HB 734 (90) Tax credit for landlords, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - HB 749 (90) Motor vehicle dealers, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - HB 767 (90) Supplemental stoplights and windshield defrosters and defoggers, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - HB 774 (90) Virginia Housing Development Authority Act, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - HB 815 (90) Testing for human immunodeficiency virus, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - HB 816 (90) Isolation of persons with communicable diseases, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - HB 830 (90) Anatomical gifts, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - HB 921 (90) Motor vehicle insurance, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - HB 940 (90) Recylcling ordinances, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - HB 950 (90) Discharge of oil, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - HB 959 (90) Virginia Mine Safety Board, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - HB 991 (90) Dept. of Motor Vehicles, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - HB 1010 (90) Disorderly conduct, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - HB 1032 (90) Radiological technology practitioners, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - HB 1042 (90) Chesapeake Bay Resource Protection Areas, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - HB 1046 (90) Pharmaceutical products - Discounts, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - HB 1055 (90) Virginia Indoor Clean Air Act, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - HB 1077 (90) Teachers - Regulations, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - HB 1100 (90) Intensified Drug Enforcement Jurisdiction, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - SB 2 (90) Craig H. Bell, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - SB 32 (90) Capital Projects - Institutions of Higher Learning, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - SB 39 (90) Individual income taxes, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - SB 55 (90) Virginia Retail Sales and Use Tax, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - SB 63 (90) Transient occupancy tax, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - SB 67 (90) Regulation of traffic, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - SB 73 (90) Board of Veterans' Affairs, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - SB 75 (90) Investment limits for insurers, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - SB 80 (90) Game Wardens - Retirement benefits, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - SB 84 (90) Board of Supervisors - Election, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - SB 89 (90) Withholding for enforcement of support, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - SB 93 (90) Senior Justices of the Supreme Court, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - SB 106 (90) Immunity from liability, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - SB 123 (90) District Courts - Acceptance of checks and credit cards, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - SB 128 (90) Motor vehicles - Buyer's orders, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - SB 131 (90) Child health supervision services - Insurance coverage, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - SB 150 (90) Virginia Indoor Clean Air Act, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - SB 171 (90) Disposition of animals, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - SB 188 (90) Line of Duty Act, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - SB 213 (90) Land subdivision, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - SB 236 (90) Unemployment Compensation Act, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - SB 239 (90) Virginia Public School Authority, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - SB 240 (90) Real property, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - SB 334 (90) Waste Management Enforcement, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - SB 340 (90) Testing for infection with human immunodeficiency virus - Prostitution, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - SB 366 (90) Virginia Transportation Contract Revenue Bonds, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - SB 370 (90) Statewide Human Services Information and Referral Program, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - SB 407 (90) Flood insurance, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - SB 411 (90) Discharge of oil, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - SB 418 (90) Sale of real estate for delinquent taxes, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - SB 464 (90) Waste management, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - SB 468 (90) Advisory Board of Respiratory Therapy, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Legislation arranged by date approved and Vetoed Legislation, 1990.
    - Legislation approved, 1990 Feb 22. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Legislation approved, 1990 Feb 28. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Legislation approved, 1990 Mar 2. (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Legislation approved, 1990 Mar 4. (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Legislation approved, 1990 Mar 5-8. (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Legislation approved, 1990 Mar 9-21. (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Legislation approved, 1990 Mar 22-23. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Legislation approved, 1990 Mar 24. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Legislation approved, 1990 Mar 26. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Legislation approved, 1990 Mar 30. (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Legislation approved, 1990 Apr 2. (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Legislation approved, 1990 Apr 3. (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Legislation approved, 1990 Apr 4. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Legislation approved, 1990 Apr 5. (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Legislation approved, 1990 Apr 6. (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Legislation approved, 1990 Apr 9. (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Legislation approved, 1990 Apr 9. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Legislation approved, 1990 Apr 9. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Legislation approved, 1990 Apr 18. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Legislation approved, 1990 May 3. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Legislation vetoed, 1990. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Special Session, 1990.
    - SB 1 (90) - Lottery sales, 1990. (Box 18, Folder 6)
- General Assembly Legislation, 1991.
  - House of Delegates Bills, 1991.
    - HB 146 (91) Dept. of Social Services - Legal services, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - HB 182 (91) Elections - Revised primary and filing schedule, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - HB 291 (91) Loaded firearms - Juveniles, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - HB 335 (91) Licensing lending institutions as insurance agents, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - HB 399 (91) School boards - Grievance procedure, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - HB 424 (91) Animal medical care facilities, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - HB 441 (91) Statewide Fire Prevention Code, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - HB 445 (91) Regulation of teachers, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - HB 480 (91) Registration rolls - Purging voters, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - HB 514 (91) Local motor vehicle licenses, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - HB 634 (91) Absentee voter ballots, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - HB 695 (91) Issuance of bonds - Borrowing money, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - HB 763 (91) Chloroflourocargons, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - HB 712 (91) Motor vehicle sunshading, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - HB 727 (91) Medical payments - Motor vehicle insurance, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - HB 729 (91) Manufacturing Licensing and Transaction Recovery Fund Law, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - HB 757 (91) Commitment hearings for the mentally ill - Fees and expenses, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - HB 792 (91) Chief Judges; Juvenile Courts; Diversionary Program, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - HB 825 (91) Board of Medicine, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - HB 852 (91) Presidential Preference Primay Election, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - HB 883 (91) Accident and sickness insurance, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - HB 981 (91) Personal watercraft safety, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - HB 1019 (91) Drug offenders - Court fees, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - HB 1074 (91) Gypsy Moth infestation, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - HB 1088 (91) Drug distribution - Penalties, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - HB 1137 (91) Vehicle warning lights, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - HB 1139 (91) Towing - Unlicensed and uninspected vehicles, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - HB 1140 (91) Coal and Gas Road Improvement Tax, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - HB 1142 (91) Proration of personal property tax, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - HB 1143 (91) Motor vehicle inspection, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - HB 1144 (91) Special license plates - Military Assault Force, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - HB 1145 (91) Witness summonses, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - HB 1142 (91) Local Agricultural and Forestral Districts Act, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - HB 1151 (91) Capital Projects - Institutions of Higher Learning, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - HB 1152 (91) Capital Projects - Institutions of Higher Learning, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - HB 1153 (91) Virginia Fair Housing Law, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - HB 1154 (91) Charter - City of Salem, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - HB 1157 (91) Default judgments, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - HB 1158 (91) Scenic River Advisory Board, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - HB 1159 (91) Workers' Compensation - Vocational rehabilitation services, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - HB 1164 (91) Possession of tobacco producets by minors, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - HB 1170 (91) Exempt Under Charitable Organization Registration Act, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - HB 1176 (91) Exemption from personal property tax - Association for the Preservation of Civil War Sites, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - HB 1178 (91) Charter - City of Falls Church, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - HB 1181 (91) Administrative Process Act, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - HB 1187 (91) Charter - Town of Kilmarnock, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - HB 1188 (91) Workers' Compensation Peer Review Committees - Compensation, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - HB 1189 (91) Easement in Rappahannock River - Contel of Virginia, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - HB 1193 (91) Charter - City of Suffolk, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - HB 1196 (91) Clarence W. Arlene W. Garrett, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - HB 1202 (91) County manager plan of government, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - HB 1204 (91) Charter - City of Danville, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - HB 1208 (91) Charter - City of Martinsville, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - HB 1210 (91) Assessment of real estate, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - HB 1213 (91) Public Procurement Act, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - HB 1215 (91) Shareholders' action - Merger or share exchange, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - HB 1218 (91) Non-stock corporations - Sale of assets, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - HB 1230 (91) County manager form of government, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - HB 1235 (91) Highway maintenance payments and matching highway funds, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - HB 1237 (91) Charter - City of Richmond, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - HB 1238 (91) Leasing of state owned land, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - HB 1240 (91) Charter - Town of Boydton, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - HB 1241 (91) Mobile Home Lot Rental Act, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - HB 1242 (91) Game Protection Fund, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - HB 1243 (91) Grievance procedure, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - HB 1245 (91) Charter - Town of Port Royal, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - HB 1246 (91) Charter - County of Chesterfield, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - HB 1247 (91) Official folk dance, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - HB 1251 (91) Charter - Incorporation of Castlewood in Russell County, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - HB 1252 (91) Marion W. Ward, Jr. - Relief, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - HB 1256 (91) Charter - Town of Chincoteague, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - HB 1259 (91) Charter and Consolidation - County of Alleghany and City of Clifton Forge, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - HB 1260 (91) Charter - Town of Dumfries, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - HB 1261 (91) Charter - Town of Tappahannock, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - HB 1268 (91) Charter - City of Staunton, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - HB 1270 (91) Residency requirement, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - HB 1272 (91) Rita Anderson - Relief, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - HB 1275 (91) Fire fighting and rescue services, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - HB 1277 (91) Virginia Public Procurement Act, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - HB 1278 (91) Residence requirements for substitute judges, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - HB 1279 (91) Physical therapists - Examinations, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - HB 1280 (91) Contractual provisions - Venue, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - HB 1281 (91) Improper operation of vessels, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - HB 1282 (91) Electronic communication systems, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - HB 1283 (91) Clerk's fees, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - HB 1284 (91) Nonsuits, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - HB 1285 (91) Corporate directors, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - HB 1286 (91) Corporate shareholder voting procedures, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - HB 1289 (91) School boards, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - HB 1292 (91) Name changes, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - HB 1297 (91) Virginia Soil and Water Conservation Board, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - HB 1301 (91) Wildlife conservation license plates, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - HB 1302 (91) Juvenile and Domestic Relations Court - Service of process, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - HB 1303 (91) Coastal Primary Sand Dune Protection Act, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - HB 1304 (91) Conservators of the Peace, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - HB 1306 (91) Assessment of real estate, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - HB 1307 (91) Inspection of official records, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - HB 1308 (91) Forfeiture in drug caes, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - HB 1310 (91) Waiver of time limits on discovery, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - HB 1311 (91) Controlled access highways, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - HB 1312 (91) Judgments - Actions on contracts, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - HB 1314 (91) Adoption jurisdictions and proceedings, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - HB 1317 (91) Tort Claims Act - Transportation districts, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - HB 1321 (91) Trespassing vehicles, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - HB 1322 (91) Voter registration, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - HB 1324 (91) Trip fishing licenses, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - HB 1327 (91) Personal watercraft - Local regulations, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - HB 1330 (91) Consolidation - Alleghany County and Clifton Forge, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - HB 1331 (91) Medical facilities - Certificate of public need, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - HB 1334 (91) Dog licenses, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - HB 1336 (91) Economic development policy, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - HB 1337 (91) Unemployment compensation, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - HB 1339 (91) Special highway construction funds, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - HB 1340 (91) Public roads - Gates and penalties, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - HB 1341 (91) Dept. for Children, Dept. for Volunteerism, Council on the Status of Women, Council on Indians, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - HB 1342 (91) Uniform Foreign Money Claims Act, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - HB 1343 (91) Mandatory release - Parole, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - HB 1350 (91) Psychiatric in-patient treatment of minors, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - HB 1353 (91) Circuit Court judges - Number, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - HB 1354 (91) Pre-sentence reports, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - HB 1355 (91) State Corporation Commission - Confidentiality of information, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - HB 1356 (91) State Corporation Commission - Power to compromise and settle, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - HB 1357 (91) Branch banks, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - HB 1358 (91) Banks - Limitations on loans, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - HB 1360 (91) Judicial Council, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - HB 1361 (91) State Treasurer, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - HB 1362 (91) Drug Control Act, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - HB 1363 (91) Commissioner of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services - Escape from custody, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - HB 1365 (91) Virginia State Bar - Advisory opinions, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - HB 1366 (91) Sales and use taxes, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - HB 1368 (91) Subdivision of land, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - HB 1369 (91) Workers' Compensation, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - HB 1371 (91) Workers' Compensation Act - Volunteers, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - HB 1372 (91) Non-resident seafood harvester licenses, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - HB 1374 (91) Ordinances - Penalties for violators, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - HB 1377 (91) Personal property tax - Proration, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - HB 1380 (91) Home/electronic incarceration programs, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - HB 1381 (91) Leasing county land, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - HB 1382 (91) Purple Heart Bridge - Occoquan River, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - HB 1384 (91) State Corporation Commission - Investigative powers, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - HB 1389 (91) Delinquent real estate taxes, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - HB 1390 (91) Persons convicted of driving under the influent, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - HB 1391 (91) Prisoners working on state and local projects, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - HB 1394 (91) Local Government Advisory Council / Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - HB 1395 (91) School boards - Salaries, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - HB 1398 (91) Transportation Trust Fund, Commonwealth Port Fund, Commonwealth Airport Fund, Commonwealth Mass Transit Fund, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - HB 1399 (91) Eminent domain - Governor / City of Richmond, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - HB 1401 (91) Pupil transportation - Board of Education, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - HB 1402 (91) Licensed nurse practioners - Prescriptive authority, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - HB 1403 (91) Regional jail or jail farm boards, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - HB 1404 (91) Jail prisoner, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - HB 1411 (91) Conditional zoning, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - HB 1412 (91) Comprehensive plan prepartion, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - HB 1413 (91) Persons convicted of a DUI offense, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - HB 1416 (91) Jail or jail farm boards, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - HB 1417 (91) Recording of releases and certificates of satisfaction, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - HB 1421 (91) Gross vehicle weight, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - HB 1427 (91) Uniform Disposition of Unclaimed Property Act, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - HB 1429 (91) Transfer of firearms - Criminal history check, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - HB 1431 (91) Regional jail and farm jail boards and jail authorities, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - HB 1432 (91) Asbestos licensure examinations, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - HB 1433 (91) Equine activity liability, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - HB 1434 (91) Local Court Service Units - Gifts by jurors, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - HB 1435 (91) Securities dealers - Registration, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - HB 1436 (91) Bank dealing with itself and affiliates, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - HB 1437 (91) Band trust subsidiaries, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - HB 1438 (91) Tax exemptions on property of elderly and handicapped, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - HB 1439 (91) Insurer investments, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - HB 1440 (91) Reformation of trusts, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - HB 1442 (91) Unsafe vehicles - Inspection and removal from highways, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - HB 1443 (91) Unsafe vehicles - Inspection and removal from highways, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - HB 1445 (91) Licensed agents and insurance consultants, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - HB 1446 (91) Investment advisor representatives, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - HB 1448 (91) Conversion of health service plans to mutual insurance companies, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - HB 1449 (91) Sewage systems and sewage treatment works, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - HB 1451 (91) Daycare programs, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 7)